Contact

jimahally@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jima-w-7a6741167 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Intra-Aortic Balloon Pump (IABP)
Ventricular Assist Devices including Impella

Continuous Renal Replacement Therapy (CRRT)

Languages

Arabic (Elementary)
Spanish (Professional Working)
Swahili (Limited Working)

Certifications

Critical Care Registered Nurse (CCRN)

Cardiac Surgery Certification (CSC)
Advanced Cardiac Life Support
(ACLS)

Honors-Awards

Sigma Theta Tau International World Refugee Woman Representative

Jima Woldegiorgis

Critical Care Registered Nurse

Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Intensive Care Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in various ICU settings, including Medical, Cardiovascular, Heart & Lung Transplant units. Skilled in management of hemodynamically unstable patients requiring mechanical intubation, multiple vasoactive/inotropic drips that may also be on either IABP, VAD (including Impella), CCO monitor and CRRT. An avid patient advocate who loves working in a multidisciplinary team setting to promote patient safety and provide quality care.

Experience

Houston Methodist
Critical Care Registered Nurse
July 2018 - Present (1 year 11 months)
Medical Center

Baylor St. Luke's Medical Center Cardiovascular Intensive Care Nurse February 2017 - Present (3 years 4 months) Medical Center

Memorial Hermann Health System Medical Intensive Care Unit RN May 2016 - October 2018 (2 years 6 months)

West Houston Medical Center Cardiac Telemetry Registered Nurse April 2015 - May 2016 (1 year 2 months) Houston

Education

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth)

Bachelor of Science in Nursing (BSN), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse